<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fen on</title><link>https://rugu.guru/docs/fen/</link><description>Recent content in Fen on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:27:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rugu.guru/docs/fen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fen install guide</title><link>https://rugu.guru/fen/fen-install-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/fen/fen-install-guide/</guid><description>We think there is a fundamental misconception about piracy. Piracy is almost always a service problem and not a pricing problem.
- Gabe Newell Fen is a Kodi add-on that allows you to easily watch movies and shows with a streaming service like experience.
This guide will show you how to setup something like the video below:
How it works # Before diving into guide let&amp;rsquo;s first take a look at how this setup works and the services you&amp;rsquo;ll need to configure it.</description></item><item><title>Installing Fen</title><link>https://rugu.guru/fen/installing-fen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/fen/installing-fen/</guid><description>After you have installed Kodi and registered a Real-Debrid and Trakt account we can start the installation process.
Navigating in Kodi # When opening Kodi for the first time this should be the screen you&amp;rsquo;re greeted to.
Kodi&amp;rsquo;s navigation centres around four navigation keys, an Enter button and a Back button.
🖥 On a computer, these keys are the navigation arrows, Enter and Backspace. Navigate to the settings page via the gear button (⚙) on the start screen.</description></item><item><title>Configuring Fen</title><link>https://rugu.guru/fen/configuring-fen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/fen/configuring-fen/</guid><description>After installing Fen we can find it in the Add-ons section of the home page. You should also see the CocoScrapers module we installed. Select Fen to open the plugin.
Authorizing accounts # Before we can start exploring any content we first need to setup some accounts. Inside Fen navigate to Tools and then TOOLS: Accounts Manager.
Here we can find some of the services that connect with Fen.</description></item><item><title>Customizing Kodi</title><link>https://rugu.guru/fen/customizing-kodi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/fen/customizing-kodi/</guid><description>For some parts of this explanation we&amp;rsquo;ll assume you are more comfortable navigating in Kodi so we&amp;rsquo;ll illustrate steps with fewer images and provide a more step-by-step approach for things we covered before like installing an addon from a repository.
Installing FENtastic # We&amp;rsquo;ll start by installing a custom skin, an add-on that changes the look and feel of Kodi.
👉 This tutorial will only cover the FENtastic a skin made specifically for the FEN plugin but there are lots of other skins you can try We&amp;rsquo;ll start by adding a new repository, by going to File Manager → Add source and entering the following url:</description></item><item><title>Subtitles</title><link>https://rugu.guru/fen/subtitles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/fen/subtitles/</guid><description>For people who want or need subtitles to enjoy media content, Kodi provides a very robust system to easily add subtitles to your files.
Installing a4kSubtitles # a4kSubtitles is a simple add-on to download subtitles from various sources on the web. We&amp;rsquo;ll use it to fetch subtitles for multiple languages or for files that don&amp;rsquo;t have subtitles embedded in them.
Start by adding a new source in File Manager called a4kSubtitles with the following url:</description></item><item><title>Tips and References</title><link>https://rugu.guru/fen/tips-and-references/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/fen/tips-and-references/</guid><description>In this last chapter, we&amp;rsquo;ll go over some tips on how to better use Fen. There&amp;rsquo;s also a reference for all the Add-ons and sources used at the bottom of the page to be easier to find for more advanced users.
Tips # Item Options and Browse # You can access an item&amp;rsquo;s options by long pressing on the item and selecting Options.... In this long press menu, you can also do some quick actions like marking the item as watched (Mark Watched Trakt) or refresh widgets.</description></item></channel></rss>