<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Seren on</title><link>https://rugu.guru/docs/seren/</link><description>Recent content in Seren on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:38:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rugu.guru/docs/seren/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Seren install guide</title><link>https://rugu.guru/seren/seren-install-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/seren/seren-install-guide/</guid><description>We think there is a fundamental misconception about piracy. Piracy is almost always a service problem and not a pricing problem.
- Gabe Newell Seren is a Kodi add-on that allows you to easily watch movies and shows with a streaming service like experience.
This guide will show you how to setup something like the video bellow:
Prerequisites # In order to start the installation process there are some services and accounts you need to configure.</description></item><item><title>Installing Seren</title><link>https://rugu.guru/seren/installing-seren/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/seren/installing-seren/</guid><description>After you have installed Kodi, and registered a Real-Debrid and Trakt account we can start the installation process.
Navigating in Kodi # After opening Kodi for the first time this should be the screen you&amp;rsquo;re greeted to.
Kodi&amp;rsquo;s navigation centers around four navigation keys, an Enter button and a Back button.
🖥 On a computer these keys are the navigation arrows, Enter and Backspace. Navigate to the settings page via the gear button (⚙) on the start screen to begin the installation process.</description></item><item><title>Configuring Seren</title><link>https://rugu.guru/seren/configuring-seren/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/seren/configuring-seren/</guid><description>After installing Seren we can find it in the Add-ons section of the home page.
Logging in to accounts # The first step is now connecting Seren to your accounts. Open Seren and navigate to settings by selecting Tools and Open Settings Menu.
In here we can find all of Seren&amp;rsquo;s settings! There are a lot of customization options, and we&amp;rsquo;ll cover some of them further ahead, but for now let&amp;rsquo;s just continue by navigating to the Accounts option on the left.</description></item><item><title>Customizing Kodi</title><link>https://rugu.guru/seren/customizing-kodi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/seren/customizing-kodi/</guid><description>For some parts of this explanation we&amp;rsquo;ll assume you are more comfortable navigating in Kodi so we&amp;rsquo;ll illustrate steps with fewer images and provide a more step by step approach for things we covered before like adding repositories and installing addons.
Installing the Arctic Horizon Skin # We&amp;rsquo;ll start by installing a custom skin, an add-on that changes the look and feel of Kodi.
👉 This tutorial will only cover the Arctic Horizon skin but there are lots of other skins you can try We&amp;rsquo;ll start by adding a new repository, by going to File Manager → Add source and entering the following url:</description></item><item><title>Subtitles</title><link>https://rugu.guru/seren/subtitles/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rugu.guru/seren/subtitles/</guid><description>For people who want or need subtitles to enjoy media content, Kodi provides a very robust system to easily add subtitles to your files.
Make subtitles appear by default # Subtitles don&amp;rsquo;t appear by default in Kodi, in order to change this behavior go to Player settings → Language and simply select a language in Preferred subtitle language option. If a file playing contains a subtitle for the selected language, it will now be displayed automatically.</description></item></channel></rss>